Watch on kissasia.li
[Road to Success]
[Episode 2]
The school's official website is
[Pay attention to mental growth]
full of punishment notices about them.
[School Bulletin Board]
Their grades are basically
at the bottom of the class as well.
No honors,
and no shot at competitions.
It seems that this time,
it's really just going to be
a one-round tour for show.
Let me just meet them openly.
Hello, teacher.
[Fu Xinshu,
former captain of the football team]
Are you the new team supervisor?
Yes, my surname is Lin.
Hello, Ms. Lin.
My name is Fu Xinshu.
"Ms. Lin"?
I've already told them to hurry up.
They should be here soon.
I bought you guys some milk tea.
You can distribute it later.
Okay, thank you, Ms. Lin.
Fu Xinshu.
Were you also on the football team before?
Yes.
What position?
I used to play midfield.
"Used to"?
What about now?
I haven't played football
for a long time now.
Wen Chengye!
So he's Wen Chengye.
[Wen Chengye,
defender of the new football team]
You know me?
You're the transfer student from Class 4.
You and your skateboard are
both very famous.
Ms. Lin, I'll go rush them again.
Hurry up. Come on.
Wen Chengye?
What? Are you here for the meeting, too?
Wen Chengye.
Please stay for the meeting.
-Who does he think he is?
-Who cares about him?
-Just ignore him, Boss.
-Yeah.
Teacher?
It's you!
There's milk tea!
-Teacher,
-How come it's her?
you bought the milk tea, didn't you?
Come and enjoy it.
Okay!
Boss, here you are.
The teacher even bought us milk tea.
She bought us milk tea.
The new teacher is so beautiful and kind.
-Fu!
-There's milk tea for us!
How come you guys arrived
even later than us?
-So what?
-So what, bro?
Feng Suo, the teacher said
[Name: Yu Ming]
[Name: Zheng Feiyang] [Name: Feng Suo]
there's no milk tea
for those who are late.
-We will... We will drink it anyway.
-Bro.
[Feng Suo,
former goalkeeper of the football team]
Master Zhi Hui was
the last one to get here,
[Zheng Feiyang,
former defender of the football team]
[Zheng Ren, former midfield player
of the football team]]
not me, right?
[Zhi Hui, former midfield player
of the football team]
Master,
which direction is lucky today?
Anyway,
it's not your position, Zheng Ren.
Mr. Zhi Hui,
how about here? How about my position?
Not good, either.
Yours is surely not...
It's definitely not your position.
It must be me,
the chosen one.
I'm sure it's not you.
There he goes again, the Master.
A one-round tour is guaranteed.
All right, enough.
Here's our team supervisor.
Ms. Lin, everyone is here...
except for Wen Chengye.
Here, I'm announcing something.
The school is arranging for you guys
to participate in a football match.
I will serve
as your temporary team supervisor.
My surname is Lin.
Football match?
At 2:30 PM this Sunday,
let's meet at the school gate to play...
in the Youth Super League qualifiers.
Our rival is Ning'an Experimental School.
Ning'an Experimental School's team is
super strong.
We definitely can't beat them.
How about we forfeit again?
Yeah, let's forfeit.
We haven't trained for 2 years.
What are we going for?
Exactly.
To make a fool of ourselves?
Our football team has been disbanded
for so long.
Why are we still playing?
Yeah, why?
-Play for what?
-I'm not going anyway.
They all seem very negative.
Those who don't show up will fail PE,
and we'll notify your parents.
I'll take down the names.
Ms. Lin, you probably
don't have that right, I think?
Director Qian gave me this right.
Fu Xinshu,
have everyone sign this later.
Fu, we've already shown you respect.
-Goodbye.
-Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Ms. Lin,
they don't care about failing,
because they fail almost every subject.
But I'll try my best
to get them all there.
Thank you.
Boss, are we really not
playing that match?
[Fight for your youth!]
The team was easily disbanded back then.
Now they want me back?
What do they take me for?
That's true, but...
Did you buy this for me?
It definitely wasn't from me.
Could it...
be from Xiaotian?
The Class Beauty wouldn't have
such bad taste, would she?
Bao Xiaotian has good taste,
having taken a liking to you, Boss.
Lin Lu, did you just call me?
Bao Xiaotian,
what do you think of my boss?
I don't know him at all.
There's a second way
to solve this question.
Can you stop being so nosy?
Don't you know girls are
easily embarrassed?
My bad, my bad.
Open it and see.
What do you think
she got me as a gift?
Are you sure it's from her?
Why wouldn't it be?
-Do you have a death wish?
-Okay, fine.
Chocolate?
And a note.
Ms. Lin,
what does this mean?
It was definitely you who did this, right?
Do you feel uncertain about your life?
Do you still not know
where your future is heading?
Lin of No. 8 High School
specializes in treating
school refusal, truancy,
lack of motivation, and poor grades.
Did you do this, too?
You really love playing pranks, Ms. Lin.
[100 free football equipment rentals]
Childish.
Not only did you give me a little gift,
but you also gave one to Chen Jianghe?
And you, bro.
You actually believed it? You're so naive.
I started working here
this Monday, September 2nd,
for the first day.
You registered last week,
before I even got here.
Furthermore,
where did you find it?
In my desk drawer.
Then tell me, my dear student, Qin Ao.
In broad daylight,
how did I go hide this chocolate
in your desk drawer without being seen?
It was computer class this morning.
So you could sneak into the classroom.
Besides, you just look like a student.
Thank you.
But I'm not into that.
I
graduated with a master's degree
from Yongchuan University.
I was our province's top liberal arts scorer
in the college entrance exam.
I have published 6 SCI papers in total—
4 as the first author.
I've received first-class scholarships
for 7 years.
If I hadn't wanted to live a life
of just getting by,
why would I have ended up sitting here?
Ms. Lin,
isn't it inappropriate for you
to brag so much?
Ms. Lin, was it really not you?
Then why is your phone number on it?
It also asks us to come to you.
It must have something to do with you.
Think it over again, Ms. Lin.
Boss, let's go over there to check it out.
There's a note
in every piece of chocolate.
What are these? I don't understand.
Nine of them have words on them.
Why doesn't this one have any?
How should I know?
Ms. Lin,
aren't you a master's graduate
from Yongchuan University,
the province's top liberal arts scorer
in the college entrance exam,
and a straight-A student who wrote
some SOS papers?
You should know, right?
It's "SCI."
I know.
The straight-A student
can't even solve this?
If I can't solve a puzzle,
there could only be two possibilities.
Firstly, it's not a puzzle at all.
Secondly, I don't
want to solve it for now.
Each sentence has a different length.
[100 free football equipment rentals]
There is a repeated word.
Is it a crossword puzzle?
[Diligence makes up for a lack of talent]
[Hard work makes the door to success]
Okay.
The grid for puzzle solving.
Got it.
[Hints about the poems]
[Diligence makes up for a lack of talent]
[Hard work makes the door to success]
Ms. Lin,
have you found anything?
[Make a great coup]
[Start over again] [Dreams come true]
"Xin-shu."
[Stay calm] [Dreams come true]
Which word do you think
should be filled in the front?
Isn't that self-evident?
It must be...
-"Fu."
What brings you here?
Hello, Ms. Lin.
What's up?
Did you guys change your mind
and decide to play
in the match this weekend?
No way!
Bro, it's daytime.
Wake up, please.
I don't play meaningless matches.
We can't win anyway.
I know.
But what if I
still want to invite you to play?
Let's get down to business.
Someone played a prank on me.
Simply put,
someone gave us a puzzle,
a crossword puzzle.
And this is our deduction process.
We've deduced
that your name goes in this blank.
[Start over again] [Make a great coup]
-"Xinshu."
-You are the one related
to Ms. Lin and us.
So the answer must be you.
Why me?
Even though he's
-the one who wants to play the most...
-We also inferred it from this hint...
Did you receive anything similar?
Judging from his reaction,
he didn't do this.
My brain hurts.
Let's go. Time to go home for dinner.
I remember now.
I did receive something.
Really?
What is it?
I'll tell you if you come to play
in the match this weekend.
Hold on.
You're still one player short
for the team, right?
I'll handle it.
[Hongjing No. 8 High School]
[Administrative Building]
I don't know how to do the homework
the teacher assigned last time.
Same here.
I've been looking it up for a long time.
Wen Chengye...
What do you want from me?
Just say it.
You left early today,
so you didn't hear it.
This Sunday afternoon at 2:30,
we'll meet at the school gate
for the match.
Can you join us?
You've waited for so long.
Is this very important to you?
Very important.
Ever since the team disbanded,
what I want to do most is
to play football with everyone once again.
I also hope you can join us
as our new teammate.
Okay.
I will definitely go
and arrive on time.
The lights are off?
So he is home.
No way,
is he bathing in the dark?
Or did he forget to turn off the water?
This guy is too weird.
Hello,
I'd like to know
about the new tenant upstairs.
I know he pays a lot of rent,
but I still need to know
his basic information, right?
If he's really that rich,
why didn't he rent a luxury apartment?
Just because he's handsome
doesn't mean he's a good person.
Come on, sir.
Just think it over.
I'm not joking with you.
Installing a bathtub in the living room
of this old residential building
and bathing in the dark—
don't you think it's so weird?
What if he's some psycho killer?
Think about how dangerous it is
for me to live here alone.
Okay.
Please make sure
you investigate this thoroughly for me.
You're still up now?
It's only 9 o'clock.
Um,
since when have you been standing here?
Not long ago.
Just since you started making that call.
That's great.
I'm used to sleeping early
and waking up early.
Then I'll get in now.
I am 30 years old,
from Yongchuan, unemployed.
Good night,
Miss Landlady.
I don't want to kill you yet.
I've only been at work for 2 days,
and I've already received 2 little gifts.
A football lending card.
A little note.
I was also asked to rebuild
the football team as the supervisor.
Who on earth is messing with me,
and why?
And the QR Code upstairs
is also weird.
Is there any connection
between them?
Do you have any idea?
Out for a morning workout?
You got the pancakes from this restaurant?
The line is usually super long.
They are freshly baked.
Try some?
No, thanks. I have a match to go to.
We still don't have everyone here yet.
Come on...
Even though I don't want to play,
I still arrived early.
In view of this pre-match gathering alone,
you can already tell today's match is
looking rough.
Are you giving up already?
What? We're obviously going to lose.
Watch your mouth.
I'm in the team.
I once dribbled past 5 players in a row
and scored with one kick.
And now?
You pant after running 2 laps.
A true hero doesn't boast of past glory.
-I mean, I can still do it now, okay?
-Keep bragging.
Ms. Lin, is there no milk tea today?
Is everyone here?
Where's Wen Chengye?
[Everyone else is here
and waiting for you.Are you almost here?]
Fu!
Are you sure
Wen Chengye promised to come today?
Is he too scared of losing to show up?
"I'm not coming, you idiot"?
[I'm not coming, you idiot.]
It's fine, Fu.
I... I'll get revenge for you later.
Great.
Ms. Lin, since Wen Chengye isn't coming,
we don't even have enough players.
Let's just disband right here.
You've got a point.
I'll go tell Director Qian.
It's time!
Why haven't you gotten on the bus?
The match is about to start!
Director Qian, here's the thing.
Wen Chengye got held up
and couldn't make it.
The team is one player short.
Can we just not go?
If he's not coming,
we'll find someone else!
What do you mean by "not go"?
The school leaders are
taking this very seriously today.
How can you just forfeit easily?
But we don't have enough players.
Then let's figure it out!
Don't pull a long face.
It's my treat today!
Come on, have some goodies.
Don't pull a long face. Give me a smile.
I bought some snacks for you.
You're usually so cute.
Don't look so down.
You usually have the brightest smile.
Come on, here you are.
Come on, come on!
-Thank you, Director.
Thank you, Director.
Here's for you.
Don't worry, just go ahead.
Leave this matter to me.
I promise before you even arrive,
the substitute will already be
waiting there for you.
Take it.
Get in the bus!
Thank you.
Hurry up! Stop dawdling!
Stop messing around. Hurry!
It's getting late!
Go! Get moving! Get on the bus!
Hurry up! Come on!
Get on! Get on now!
This bus is pretty fancy.
And they're well-equipped.
I'm so jealous.
-Thank you, Coach.
-Hurry up!
-Come on!
Their conditions are way too good.
That's a bit too much.
They're so delicate.
Hurry up.
Let me take this.
Boss, I want this treatment, too.
Then you should ask Ms. Lin for it.
What supplies do we have?
I ordered some water for you
from a nearby farmhouse.
Oh, God...
Let's go.
Here we are.
Come on, get off.
Relax and play well.
-Okay!
-Okay.
When did we get another football team?
They came for the chemistry competition,
taking the test
in the building over there.
Chemistry has always been
Hongjing's strongest subject
in competitions.
I'm coming!
Chen Weidong
from the track and field team?
I came right after Director Qian
talked to me.
So everyone's here. Let's go.
-Let's go.
[Yongchuan Provincial Youth Super League]
Stop there.
[Hongjing No. 8 High School vs.
Ning'an Experimental School]
Everyone, show your faces.
Why bother taking photos
if it's going to be a one-round tour?
She was probably
just completing a photo task
assigned by Director Qian.
Ms. Lin,
can I really do it?
Chen Weidong,
we never thought about winning.
Why are you taking it so seriously?
Bro, Wen Chengye didn't come,
but you did.
You have my respect.
Ning'an united,
fighting only for the championship!
Should we also come up
with a slogan together?
What's there to think about?
We're just here to run a few laps,
lose the game, and put on a show.
Then we have to put on a full show.
Come on.
Who can come up with a slogan?
Qi Liang, let Qi Liang do it.
Why don't you do it?
Aren't you always talkative?
Then I'll come up with one.
Hongjing, Hongjing, shining stars!
-That's so tacky.
-Oh...
Then you think of one.
Gather here.
If you don't join me,
I'll tell Director Qian about it.
There you go again,
bringing up Director Qian.
Come on.
Director Qian.
Hongjing, Hongjing, shining stars!
-Hongjing, Hongjing...
Say it louder.
-Hongjing, Hongjing,
-shining stars!
Let's go.
Today's match is about to start.
[Yongchuan Provincial Youth Super League]
[Hongjing No. 8 High School vs.
Ning'an Experimental School]
The two teams are
Ning'an Experimental School
and Hongjing No. 8 High School.
The match officially begins.
First up, there's a coin toss
to choose sides.
The ones in blue and black striped uniforms
are from Ning'an Experimental School.
Their team is extremely fast
and known as the "Cheetahs."
The team in the blue jerseys is
Hongjing No. 8 High School.
They haven't participated
in any match for 2 years.
In fact, just 2 months without playing
can completely change a team.
And they've been absent for 2 whole years.
In the football fans' eyes,
their chances of winning look slim.
The 2 forwards
of Hongjing No. 8 High School
are No. 9, Qin Ao,
and No. 7, Chen Jianghe.
Chen Jianghe is
good at one-touch finishing in the box.
As for Qin Ao,
he's good at using changes of pace
to pull off one-on-one dribbles.
This is
Hongjing No. 8 High School's goalkeeper,
No. 1, Feng Suo.
He is the team's last line of defense.
Hongjing's 2 core defenders
are No. 6, Lin Lu, and No. 5, Yu Ming.
Because of his small stature, Lin Lu was
once jokingly called
a player who'd jump up
and shatter your knees.
Next to him is Yu Ming,
capable of charging down the flanks.
The 2 teams are making
their final pre-match preparations.
I wonder if it's because the ones
from Hongjing No. 8 High School
haven't played for so long,
but they look a bit loose.
QR Code?
What is he doing here?
Come on! Go for it!
Mark your men
and watch the timing!
Come on!
The match begins!
Ning'an Experimental School's team
kicks off.
Their passing speed is very fast.
Hongjing No. 8 High School
stands no chance
to intercept the ball.
The situation is instantly
under Ning'an Team's control.
-Hongjing No. 8 High School's captain,
-Mark him!
No. 10 Fu Xinshu,
is like Hongjing's midfield engine.
He commands the team's defense
and is the heart
of the entire Hongjing Team.
I didn't expect to be
this fun participating
in such a high school league.
These kids aren't entirely useless.
It's so passionate!
This is their true battlefield.
I suddenly feel that
football is actually quite fun.
Shoot!
So fast? Has it even been a minute?
They can't be this bad, right?
[Ning'an Experimental School 01]
[Hongjing No. 8 High School 00]
Goal! One to zero.
Ning'an Experimental School
scored the first goal.
The Hongjing No. 8 High School's players
look nowhere near as good as before.
During the 2 years they haven't competed,
did they do nothing but sleep?
Hongjing No. 8 High School is
in very poor form.
After the goal,
the team members
seem to have started blaming each other.
No. 9 Qin Ao and No. 6 Lin Lu
miscommunicated.
Yeah,
there's still time!
Go for it!
-Captain Fu Xinshu is passing the ball.
-Watch the ball!
But the ball has been intercepted!
The ball!
Ning'an shoots!
The ball was saved by Feng Suo!
The ball is once again
with Hongjing No. 8 High School.
Number 9, Qin Ao,
with his individual skill,
has dribbled the ball
into the penalty area.
Shoot!
Unfortunately, it was also saved
by Ning'an's goalkeeper.
Both sides have exchanged
attacks and defenses,
neither gaining an absolute advantage.
The running speed of both teams' players
has noticeably slowed down on the field.
Lack of endurance
has always been Ning'an's weakness.
However, Hongjing Team has clearly
lacked training for 2 years,
and their stamina is also
failing to keep up.
Why is he still here?
Could it be that he
also likes watching football matches?
You know about football, too?
A little bit.
Watch the game.
Hongjing's No. 10 is advancing
at high speed with the ball.
The 2 players collided for the ball,
and the ball was intercepted!
They crashed into each other.
Fu Xinshu was knocked down,
falling heavily to the ground.
The right side!
Ning'an
dribbled past Hongjing's No. 5, Yu Ming.
He's still advancing.
Hongjing Team's No. 12
used his body to block,
but the referee blew the whistle!
-Looks like No. 12 committed a handball!
-Calm down, calm down.
It was my shoulder that hit the ball.
What's happening?
The referee thinks
your defending player
opened his arms
in the opponent's penalty area,
and his arm touched the ball,
so a penalty kick was awarded.
So did he actually commit a handball?
From my angle,
no.
-What? Do that again, and you're off.
-Alright, it's okay.
He even blew the whistle for that.
Let's go.
What should we do in this situation?
This is the first lesson for you—
obey the referee's decisions.
The first lesson for me?
So pretentious.
Never mind.
We're just
going through the motions anyway.
The referee has finally ruled
that Hongjing's No. 12, Chen Weidong,
handled the ball
and awarded a penalty kick to Ning'an.
Possession goes back to Ning'an.
Next is a tense penalty kick.
Ning'an Team's No. 14 is
standing at the penalty mark.
It's a test for the goalkeeper, Feng Suo.
Run-up, shoot!
It's in again.
Two to zero.
Ning'an Experimental School
extends its lead.
For Hongjing No. 8 High School,
this is like a blatant slap in the face.
We shouldn't have come here
to embarrass ourselves!
Your safety comes first.
[Ning'an Experimental School 02]
[Hongjing No. 8 High School 00]
Are you trying to discipline us
or save us?
Sorry,
we are just lousy students.
Please stay away from us.
They may look careless and carefree,
talking like winning or losing
doesn't matter.
But in fact,
their faces clearly show
their unwillingness to lose,
their anger,
and their helplessness.
Going through the motions?
It doesn't look like that.
Do they really not want to win?
Lin Lu, are you alright?
-I'm fine. Let's continue!
-Are you okay?
No.
These kids who say they don't care
actually do care.
They really want to win.
They yearn for victory
more than anyone else.
The fire burning in their eyes,
the relentless futile efforts,
yet the refusal to stop running—
none of them can be faked.
Do you want to win?
[Receive Money by QR Code]
[Loading]
[Pay to Individual]
♪ There's nothing to fear ♪
♪ Because you're with me ♪
♪ The light shimmers ♪
♪ Brilliant as stars ♪
♪ Running towards you ♪
♪ I keep moving fearlessly ♪